# Benny Hassan, Full Stack Developer

bennyh960@gmail.com | 052-4874600 | LinkedIn | Portfolio | 0

#### **Profile**

Full Stack Developer with 2 years of experience in both Front-End and Back-End technologies. Previously a Chemical Engineer (B.Sc.) with strong technical, analytical, and project management skills. Highly motivated, self-taught, and collaborative with experience in React, .Net, Node and AWS/Azure services.

## **Experience**

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER | DELOITTE | SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

- · Developing efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of client
- · Creating innovative and adaptable solutions for a diverse range of clients.
- · Developing in fast paced environment with several projects at hand
- **Global Project Management Application Development**, Led the development of time-sensitive features handling global time zones. Technologies: React, .NET Core, MongoDB, Azure DevOps, Agile
- Microservices Architecture POC Leadership, managed a team to develop a financial transaction system using microservices. Technologies: .NET, React, PostgreSQL, AWS (Cognito, SQS, ECS, EC2, S3, API Gateway), Docker

#### PROCESS ENGINEER | INTEL | 04/2018 - 02/2022

· Tool owner of production machines, responsible for tool performance, data, writing work plans, troubleshooting, validation, quality performance and project management.

## PROCESS ENGINEER | MERCK | 04/2016 - 04/2018

· Project management includes design and development technological production processes, problemsolving, and improving product process and quality.

## **Education**

B.SC. IN CHEMICAL ENGINEERING | SCE | DECEMBER 2015 | GPA: 93

#### FULL STACK BOOTCAMP | APPLESEEDS | SEPTEMBER 2022 | EXCELLENCE AWARD

### **Skills & Abilities**

• Front-End: React, Html, CSS

• **Back-End**: Node JS, .Net , Python

· Database: Postgres, MongoDB

· Cloud: AWS, Azure

- · Interpersonal Communication
- · Creative Problem Solving
- · Others: Git, OpenAI, Microservices, TypeScript

# Languages

Hebrew - Native Speaker

English - Highly Proficient